[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "25 x 25",
        "choices": [800, 250, 600, 625],
        "correct": 100
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "400 x 2",
        "choices": [800, 666, 402, 799],
        "correct": 800
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "44 x 2 x 1",
        "choices": [120, 88, 98, 100],
        "correct": 88
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "30 x 30 x 1",
        "choices": [999, 960, 955, 940],
        "correct": 900
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "222 x 2",
        "choices": [444, 420, 160, 800],
        "correct": 444
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "100 x 1 x 5",
        "choices": [400, 200, 600, 500],
        "correct": 500
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "500 x 2",
        "choices": [2000, 1000, 1110, 1300],
        "correct": 1000
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "700 x 2",
        "choices": [800, 1400, 900, 1500],
        "correct": 1400
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "350 x 2",
        "choices": [700, 660, 600, 800],
        "correct": 700
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "80 x 1",
        "choices": [88, 90, 88, 39],
        "correct": 80
    }
]